

# ARIA SENA TRIMULIA FRONTEND ENGINEERING / IT SUPPORT

Malang, Indonesia | Phone / Whatsapp / Telegram: +6285730037568 | Email: ariast390@gmail.com | Linkedin: Aria Sena Trimulia | Instagram: @aria\_st

#### **SUMMARY**

I'm a university student who has some expertise in IT, coding and networking. Have high self-confidence and don't give up easily. Having direct work experience and being able to solve problems quickly and thoroughly. I like to learn and challenge myself to try new things and want to continuously improve my knowledge and skills.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## **Generasi GIGIH 2.0 By GOTO**

Front-End Engineer Student (Feb 2022 - Present)

- frontend engineer Student training made by the GOTO company
- This program lasts for 5 full months (3months technical skills training, soft skills and career readiness, 2months capstone project/intern)
- Learning about javascript coding, ReactJS, Typescript, and many more.

### Se'i Sapi Maitua

(Jan 2021 - Feb 2022)

#### Kitchen Staff

(Jan 2021 - Feb 2021)

- Cook a variety of menus in the restaurant
- > Prepare quality ingredients for restaurants
- > Keep the meat fresh when served

#### Stand Keeper

(Mar 2021 – Jan 2022)

- Promoted and given the responsibility of maintaining the outlet
- > Take care of the food stands in the food court and serving food to customers
- > Prepare tools and food ingredients
- Calculate expanse and income from stand everyday

#### Warkop Kopi Rakjat

Contract Employee (Nov 2020 - Dec 2020)

- Work as a temporary
- Make coffee and deliver to customers and keeping the cafe environment clean
- · Establish relationship with customers

## **Bingsoo Dessert and Resto**

Part-Timer Bar & waiter (Dec 2019 – Sep 2020)

- Make a korean dessert
- · Serving dishes aesthetically and perfecly to the customer
- · Following protocol hygine on the restaurant
- Ensure that everything served is fresh when it arrives at customers

#### **Direktorat Jenderal Pajak Jatim III**

Internship IT Technician Support (Jun 2018 – Dec 2018)

- I did practical work when I was in vocational school
- my job was to fix a computer problems
- fix the office internet network, and make LAN lines
- I also input data to the office data server and make various kinds of letters

### **EDUCATION**

## **UNIVERSITAS Merdeka Malang (2019 - Present)**

Information Systems - GPA 3.74

## **SMK Negeri 6 Malang (2017 – 2019)**

Computer and Network Engineering / TKJ

## **SKILLS**

- Microsoft Office word, Excel, PPT/Powerpoint
- Programming language HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT
- Copywriting
- ReactJS Javascript library
- Website Builder / Elementor
- Data Entry
- Networking Maintenance / Troubleshooting
- Cook
- Hardware and software maintenance
- Installation hardware, software, and network
- MYSQL Database

## **COURSE AND CERTIFICATIONS**

- HTML & CSS Course By Progate
- <u>Javascript Course</u>
   <u>By Progate</u>
- GIT Course
  By Progate